Oh, [gasps]
I think my allergies are acting up.
Oh.
>> [snorts and laughter]
>> No wonder.
Now, if I give you this treat, you'd
better not tell your ma, you hear?
Cassidy, you're going to teach her to
beg.
Aw, but she has been so good lately,
hasn't she?
I have heard that cats can be quite
temperamental, but Vika seems very
friendly. They aren't always the nicest.
I think she just really likes you.
Are you speaking to me?
Hm,
perhaps I should prioritize cat on my
list of languages to learn.
You're so cute, I could just squish you
to bits.
>> [snorts]
>> Nah, don't worry. I'm just pulling your
tail.
So, I'm trying to ask everybody this,
what is your favorite animal?
Uh, yeah, I can see it.
How about you fly me up and I'll make it
rain fire.
A cat in a jetpack?
YOU'VE GOT TO BE KITTEN ME.
>> [laughter]
>> REINHARDT, I DO BELIEVE IT'S kitten me.
DON'T BE RIDICULOUS, SHE'S NOT A BABY.
AH, if only you were a black cat, you
could help me ward off evil.
Sorry, jeez. You're fine the way you
are, okay?
Intelligent, adaptable,
you have the makings of a perfect test
subject.
Though an added dose of obedience would
be appreciated.
How delightful to see human arrogance
contradicted
by a cat, no less.
Zebedelah hates WILL BE PERILOUS.
SHARPEN THOSE CLAWS, FIKA.
Or perhaps our enemy will change their
ways when they see HOW CUTE YOU ARE.
BRIGITTA, you're one of my best agents,
so I'll give you one chance to explain
why you put a cat in a jetpack. I know
it seems crazy, but she can help. Can't
you, Fika? Aw, good girl.
I should have stayed retired.
You'd better stay out of trouble out
there, understand, recruit?
And I'll know if you've been sneaking
treats between missions.
Fika, were you playing on my desk again?
You accidentally tripped my security
systems.
Aw, it's okay. I'll find you something
else to play with.
Aw, hey little guy, come here.
>> [snorts]
>> Oh, uh
sorry.